http://www.waterfordstanley.com/privacy-security/

Contact our Experts on 051 302 300
Main Navigation
Stanley Heat Pumps
Why Stanley Heat Pumps?
PRIVACY & SECURITY
Waterford Stanley Ltd is committed to safeguarding your privacy. This policy explains what information we collect and how we use the personal information you supply to us.
In using our website, any of our services or providing us with any personal information we will assume you are agreeing to your information being used and disclosed in the ways described in this policy.
1. WHO WE ARE?
Waterford Stanley Ltd is Ireland’s leading manufacturer and provider of cast-iron cookers and stoves and distributor of Rangemaster appliances. Waterford Stanley Ltd has been bringing warmth and comfort to homes for generations, stretching back to when the first range cooker was made in Waterford in 1936.
The company is registered in Ireland under Registered Number 84827 and its head office address is Unit 401, Waterford Industrial Estate, Cork Road, Waterford X91 DR76.
Waterford Stanley Ltd is a wholly owned subsidiary of the Middleby Corporation, which is registered at 1400 Toastmaster Drive, Elgin, Illinois, USA. 60120
2. Data Protection Act
In carrying out our day-to-day activities we process and store personal information relating to our customers and are therefore required to adhere to the requirements of all data protection legislation, including the EU Data Protection Directive 95/46/EC, the EU General Data Protection Regulation 2016/679 (applicable from May 2018), the EU e-Privacy Directive 2002/58/EC and any relevant national implementing legislation and any substantially similar local legislation, including the guidance, codes of practice, recommendations and deliberations of the relevant supervisory authority, in each case as amended or replaced from time to time.
We take our responsibilities under these acts very seriously and are always striving to ensure the personal information we obtain is held, used, transferred or otherwise processed in accordance with these acts.
3. WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?
You can access our website home pages and browse our website without disclosing your personal data.
When you register with us, go all or part-way through the process of placing an order or request information from us, you will be asked to provide certain information such as your name, address, details of your credit card (only if you are placing an order and paying by credit card) and your telephone number and email address so we can process and fulfil your information request or order and notify you of your order status.
We will maintain records of the orders and services you have requested from us and we will also store information about what consents you have given to receive, for example, special offers, news and product updates.
We do not store any credit card details on our systems. Such information is only used to process your payment via credit card processing companies.
4. USE OF COOKIES AND TAGS
Our websites make use of ‘cookies’ and ‘tags’ to help track our online activity and monitor usage of our websites. The information they collect and share is anonymous and does not personally identify you. They do not track and store your name, address, telephone number or email address.
To learn more about our ‘cookies’ and ‘tags’ please read our Cookies Policy
5. HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION
We are permitted to use the information we collect about you to:
Administer our websites
Monitor customer traffic patterns and site usage to help us develop and improve the design and layout of our sites
To get your feedback
Where you have given consent, we may:
Send you information such as company news, new products, special offers and events
Offer you entry to our competitions
We will only send you marketing information by mail or email.
6. WHO WE WILL SHARE THE INFORMATION WITH?
Without your explicit consent, we will never pass on your personal details to anyone outside Waterford Stanley Ltd for them to use for their own marketing purposes.
In order to serve you most efficiently, we may share your information with reputable third-party companies. These include fulfilment and distribution institutions that handle our order fulfilment, service organisations carrying out repair work on our behalf, fraud prevention and credit checking agencies, our auditors and our parent company which reviews and audits our processes.
These organisations are under strict obligations to keep your personal information private.
7. PROTECTING YOUR PERSONAL DATA
All information we collect about our customers is held on secure servers. In situations where these servers are externally hosted we will only use reputable hosting companies which adhere to security policies and procedures at least as stringent as our own.
8. YOUR PASSWORDS
Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone. When you create a password, it should be a minimum of seven characters long and use a mix of numbers and characters. You should avoid using obvious phrases like ‘password’, your name or phone number.
9. STOPPING COMMUNICATION FROM US
If you decide you no longer want us to contact you, please visit our website and click on the unsubscribe link.
When you unsubscribe we will act quickly, but you may continue to receive mailings for a short while for items already in preparation or on their way to you.
Please note that if you unsubscribe and subsequently request information then we will still send you information to fulfil your request.
10. LEGAL ENFORCEMENT
We may share your data with other organisations if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data to comply with any legal obligation or to enforce or apply our terms of use as set out in our Terms and Conditions and other agreements. Information may also be shared to protect the rights, property or safety of Waterford Stanley Ltd, our customers or others.
11. THIRD-PARTY SITES
Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.
12. MONITORING COMMUNICATIONS
As part of our efforts to make further improvements to the service we provide to our customers, telephone calls to and from us may be recorded or monitored and used for training purposes. To protect the operation of our computer systems we monitor both incoming and outgoing email.
13. YOUR RIGHTS UNDER THE DATA PROTECTION ACT
You have the right to:
Ask us to remove your personal information from our records
Update or amend the information we hold about you if it is wrong
Object to the processing of your information for marketing purposes
Request a copy of the information we hold about you
Raise a concern or complaint about the way in which your information is being used.
14. CONTACT US
If you wish to find out more about your rights or obtain a copy of the information we hold about you, please email DataProtection@WaterfordStanley.com quoting Security and Privacy Enquiry. Alternatively, you can write to us at:
Data Protection Officer, Waterford Stanley Ltd.,Unit 401 Waterford Industrial Estate,Cork Road,Waterford.X91 DR76
As instructed in GDPR policy we will furnish your data within 30 days of verifying your identification.
15. CHANGES TO THE SECURITY AND PRIVACY POLICY
We keep our Security and Privacy Policy under regular review. This privacy policy was last updated April 2018. If we make changes to this policy, we will notify you by updating the policy on our websites.
Brochure Request
Stockist
Social Networks with Waterford Stanley
Close Window
Social Sharing
Follow us via your social network
Share this page via your social network
Click on the link below to see our blog
Read our blog
Newsletter sign up | Join our email list to receive our latest news and offers
Sign up to our Newsletter
WEEE Directive
Privacy & Security
Terms of Website Use
Sitemap
Cookie Policy
Ethical Trading Policy
©2019 Stanley is a Registered Trademark of Waterford Stanley Limited. Registered in Ireland under Registered Number 84827. Unit 401- 403, Waterford Industrial Estate, Cork Road, Waterford, X91 DR76, Ireland.
Waterford Stanley Ltd 2019
Part of
More Links
STANLEY HEAT PUMPS
Why Stanley Heat Pumps
Heat Pumps Explained
Heat Pump Models & Accessories
Resource Centre
Why Stanley Stoves?
